Guide to the Yasser Alwan Collection AD.MC.002
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Series II: Egypt, 1895-1971 (Box 1-7)
  - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series, 1412
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - The Head of the Colussus of Rameses II, at the Thebian Necropolis. 10.9 x 6.9 cm, 27 February 1926; cuid909 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Photographic Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Arabic Writing; Statues/Sculptures; Gelatin Silver Prints; Luxor, Egypt; Thebes, Egypt; Men; Individual Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two boys boxing. 6.1 x 9.2 cm, Undated; cuid910 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Children; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Boys; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A man in a tarbouche standing in the garden. 11.5 x 8.0 cm, 1933; cuid911 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Gardens; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Ismailia, Egypt; Facial Hair; Hats
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A young man wearing a tarbouche and a bow tie, rubber stamps on image. 5.9 x 4.8 cm, 1938; cuid912 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Photographic Prints; Bow Ties; Men; Arabic Writing; Fez/Tarboush; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Postal Stamps; Facial Hair; Signatures; Hats
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Children on the beach playing with sand. 6.5 x 6.5 cm, Undated; cuid913 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Beaches; Children; Boys; Egypt; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A baby being held by an adult. 6.5 x 6.5 cm, Undated; cuid914 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group on a balcony, over looking the sea (linked ref1002). 6.4 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid915 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Men; Telephones; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Seas; Photographic Prints; Women; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two men and a woman standing on a balcony, near the beach (linked ref942). 6.4 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid916 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Regional/National Dress; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Group Portraits; Seas
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Five children in a field. 6.5 x 9.4 cm, Undated; cuid917 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Horses; Animals; Girls; Countryside/Rural; Boys; Group Portraits; Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Men sitting in chairs, listening to a speech celebrating prophet Mohamed's birth at Al Abbassiya secondary school (linked ref945). 6.4 x 9.0 cm, 1949; cuid918 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Speeches; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Audiences/Spectators; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Men; Arabic Writing; Cairo, Egypt; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Hats
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group portrait of a man and a woman with six children. 9.0 x 6.2 cm, 1949; cuid919 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Men; Arabic Writing; Alexandria, Egypt; Group Portraits; Children; Boys; Girls; Women; Fez/Tarboush; Hats
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A family group pose on a rooftop. 6.1 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid920 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Photographic Prints; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Women; Men; Children; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Three girls wearing matching outfits stnd beside a man and an ox. 6.4 x 6.4 cm, Undated; cuid921 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Animals; Cattle/Cows; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Girls; Gelatin Silver Prints; Countryside/Rural; Buildings; Group Portraits; Children
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Men sitting at a café in front of Cinema Empire, a boy sits beneath the table. A banner for the films Monsieur Albert and L'Illusion Perdue is in the background. 5.9 x 8.4 cm, Circa 1932; cuid922 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Cinema; Egypt; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Bicycles/Tricycles; Men; Restaurants/bars; Actors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Boys; Children; Workers; Transportation; Fez/Tarboush; Films; French Writing; Advertisements; Hats; Turbans
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Men and women in a park 6.2 x 8.7 cm, 1962; cuid923 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Egypt; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Parks; Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A girl holding a brush. 9.6 x 6.4 cm, Undated; cuid924 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Egypt; Buildings; Individual Portraits; Children; Photographic Prints; Girls; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A woman in a strapless dress, looking off camera. 8.6 x 5.6 cm, Undated; cuid925 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Photographic Prints; Women; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Jewelry; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two men in a photo booth, one in military uniform. 4.5 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid926 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Photo Booth; Men; Arabic Writing; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Medals/Insignia; Facial Hair
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A young woman on the telephone in a photo booth. 4.9 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid927 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Photo Booth; Telephones; Individual Portraits; Jewelry; Women
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two women embracing in a photo booth. 4.5 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid928 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Photo Booth; Women; Group Portraits; Jewelry
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A woman wearing a beret, posing in a photo booth. 4.7 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid929 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Jewelry; Hats; Girls; Photographic Prints; Photo Booth; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Individual Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group of women and girls with musical instruments. 6.2 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid930 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Pianos; Girls; Women; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Oud; Group Portraits; Children
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A young woman in a white shirt and dark vest. 8.0 x 5.0 cm, 1932; cuid931 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Women
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A girl in a school uniform. 8.2 x 5.2 cm, Undated; cuid932 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Uniforms; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Girls; Jewelry; Students; Children
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A woman seated on a sofa with a full face veil. 9.9 x 6.4 cm, Undated; cuid933 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Furnishings; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Jewelry
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two women in the garden. 11.0 x 6.4 cm, Undated; cuid934 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Gardens; Photographic Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Egypt; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A boy leaning on a table. 8.9 x 6.8 cm, Undated; cuid935 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Photographic Prints; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Fez/Tarboush; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Egypt; Furnishings; Hats; Carpets/Rugs
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A woman leaning on a piece of furniture. 11.2 x 6.8 cm, Undated; cuid936 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Egypt; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A man sitting in front of a large plant. 8.9 x 6.3 cm, Undated; cuid937 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Egypt; Individual Portraits; Parks; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A young man standing in front of two cannons. 6.4 x 8.8 cm, 1931; cuid938 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Egypt; Buildings; Individual Portraits; English Writing; Cannons; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Weapons
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A man sitting with crossed legs in a garden. 8.7 x 6.0 cm, 7 September 1935; cuid939 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Men; Fez/Tarboush; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A cyclist riding a bicycle. 9.0 x 6.4 cm, 15 October 1933; cuid940 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Bicycles/Tricycles; Men; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Sports
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A man reaching the top of the one of the Pyramids, possibly the Pyramid of Khafre. 9.0 x 5.9 cm, Undated; cuid941 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids; Men; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Individual Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Men and boys standing in front of a building. 6.3 x 8.8 cm, 28th October 1934; cuid942 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Fez/Tarboush; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Group Portraits; Men; Boys; Children; Hats
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group of young men outside a large complex. 6.5 x 9.1 cm, 21st of March 1937; cuid943 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Boys; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Children; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Signatures
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group with some officials walking through a rural area. 6.8 x 11.3 cm, 22 October 1933; cuid944 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Countryside/Rural; Oases; Turbans; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fez/Tarboush; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Arabic Writing; Men; Aswan, Egypt; Boys; Children; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Group Portraits; Hats
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A man and woman sitting on deck chairs on the beach. 7.4 x 11.6 cm, Undated; cuid945 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Photographic Prints; Beaches; Egypt; Men; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Five men on a hill overlooking the Nile. 8.5 x 11.2 cm, 11 November 1926; cuid946 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Countryside/Rural; Nile River; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Deserts; Men; Arabic Writing; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two men standing next to a palm tree. 8.6 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid947 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Photographic Prints; Oases; Outdoors; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Regional/National Dress; Egypt; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two men playing ping-pong/table tennis on a terrace. Same man from ref1032. 6.5 x 10.4 cm, 17 February 1937; cuid948 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Photographic Prints; Sports; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; French Writing; Egypt; Buildings; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Four men in tarbouches, sitting on wicker chairs on a terrace. 5.9 x 5.9 cm, Undated; cuid949 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings; Fez/Tarboush; Men; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Buildings; Facial Hair; Hats
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group in a small boat on the Nile. 8.9 x 6.2 cm, Undated; cuid950 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Women; Men; Boats/Ships; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Nile River; Egypt; Children
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - An athlete throwing a discus. 9.2 x 6.5 cm, Undated; cuid951 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Buildings; Photographic Prints; Audiences/Spectators; Men; Sports; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Individual Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Men wearing party hats. 8.3 x 5..9 cm, UNdated; cuid952 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Egypt; Waiting staff/Servers; Books; Group Portraits; Hats; Parties; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two boys in bathing suits, standing in front of a building. 8.9 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid953 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Boys; Egypt; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group of men in lab coats, in a room with a painted stucco wall in the background (linked ref1036). 9.4 x 6.5 cm, Undated; cuid954 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Men; Egypt; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Lab Coats; Group Portraits; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Frescoes; Doctors
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group of men, some in lab coats standing in front of some frescoes (linked ref980). 9.4 x 6.5 cm, Undated; cuid955 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Men; Egypt; Frescoes; Group Portraits; Buildings; Facial Hair
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Four women in front of the Sphynx and the Pyramids of Giza. 8.6 x 5.8 cm, 25 January 1930; cuid956 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Giza, Egypt; Women; Photographic Prints; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Pyramids; French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - The interior of the Sforzesco Castle in Milan, Italy. 6.6 x 9.4 cm, 15 September 1934; cuid957 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Architecture; Statues/Sculptures; French Writing; Milan, Italy; Forts/Castles; Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A woman at the beach (same location as ref989). 4.0 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid958 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Photographic Prints; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Women; Seas; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Individual Portraits; Children; Boys; Water
  - Curly-Haired Woman Series, 1413
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A woman holding a veil over her face in a photo booth (same woman as ref987). 4.8 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid959 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Photo Booth; Costumes; Head Covers/Veils; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Women; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - The woman from ref984 when she was a child. 6.1 x 4.1 cm, Undated; cuid960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Girls; Egypt; Photo Booth; Individual Portraits; Children
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A man wearing a tarbouche, looking off camera. 4.6 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid961 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Fez/Tarboush; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Photo Booth; Men; Photographic Prints; Hats
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A young woman, posing with a white veil over her head (same woman as ref984). 4.3 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid962 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Costumes; Photographic Prints; Photo Booth; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Jewelry
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A woman walking on the sidewalk, a building named 'Victoria House' is in the background.4.2 x 3.6 cm, Undated; cuid963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Photographic Prints; Cars/Trucks; Streets/Roads; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Egypt; Signs/Signposts; Buildings; Street Lamps; Transportation
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A woman on the pier by the beach (same location as ref983). 4.1 x 3.5 cm, Undated; cuid964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Women; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Beaches; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Seas; Individual Portraits
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A group sitting under a parasol at the beach. 4.0 x 3.6 cm, Undated; cuid965 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Group Portraits; Women; Men; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Umbrellas/Parasols
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A woman posing on the dock. 4.0 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid966 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Women; Egypt
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A young woman looking off camera. 4.7 x 3.8 cm, 1952; cuid967 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Women; Arabic Writing
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A young woman, posing with her hands under her chin. 4.5 x 3.8 cm, Undated; cuid968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Photographic Prints; Photo Booth; Women; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt
  - Mansour Beih Series, 1414
    - Mansour Beih Series - Six men having a picnic (same handwriting on reverse as ref1082). 7.2 x 11.4 cm, Undated; cuid1053 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Food; Parks; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Picnic; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Alcohol; Arabic Writing; Drinks/Beverages
    - Mansour Beih Series - Notre Dame Cathedral of Paris, France (same handwriting on reverse as ref1081). 7.2 x 11.5 cm, Undated; cuid1054 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Buildings; Notre Dame de Paris; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Churches; Paris, France; Arabic Writing; Religious Sites
    - Mansour Beih Series - A man wearing leather gloves, holding a hat. 11.1 x 6.7 cm, 31 May 1927; cuid1055 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Rivers; Men; Paris, France; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Signatures
    - Mansour Beih Series - A man wearing a dark coat and bowler hat on a bridge (linked ref1085, ref1086, ref1087 and ref1090). 11.0 x 8.4 cm, 22-1-1926; cuid1056 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Buildings; France; Hats; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Rivers; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - Two men in coats and hats, with the Place de la Concorde and the Luxor obelisk in the background (linked ref1084). 7.7 x 10.4 cm, Undated; cuid1057 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Fountains; Paris, France; Place de la Concorde; Photographic Prints; Hats; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - A man in striped jacket, reclining on a lawn with a two story building behind him (same handwriting ref1084 and ref1090). 10.3 x 7.5 cm, 1926; cuid1058 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Egypt; Arabic Writing; Buildings; Men; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sandhurst, Berkshire, UK; Facial Hair; Signatures
    - Mansour Beih Series - A man in a suit standing in front of the Luxor obelisk in the Place de la Concorde, Paris, France same man ref1086). 11.0 x 8.3 cm, Undated; cuid1059 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Place de la Concorde; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Paris, France
    - Mansour Beih Series - Three men posing at the foot of some stairs. 6.8 x 11.2 cm, Undated; cuid1060 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; France; Egypt; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - A view the Ponte Alexander III in Paris, France. 6.9 x 11.3 cm, Undated; cuid1061 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Paris, France; Bridges; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Rivers
    - Mansour Beih Series - A soldier standing in front of Sandhurst College (same handwriting as ref1084 and ref1086). 10.3 x 7.7 cm, March 1926; cuid1062 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; France; Buildings; Individual Portraits; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Egypt; Men; Sandhurst, Berkshire, UK; Facial Hair; Signatures
    - Mansour Beih Series - Four men and a woman with a white fur, standing in front of a house (linked ref1088 and ref1095). 11.3 x 6.8 cm, 1928; cuid1063 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Fur Garments; Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Arabic Writing; Houses; Group Portraits; Buildings; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - A man standing in front of a fountain with some large buildings in the background.(same handwriting as ref1091). 6.8 x 11.3 cm, 6-1-1929; cuid1064 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Photographic Prints; Egypt; Hats; Men; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Paris, France; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - Two men in suits sitting in a room with wallpaper. 6.3 x 8.4 cm, Undated; cuid1065 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Men; Houses; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - Two men in suits sitting in a cafe. Same man from ref1099. 5.2 x 8.0 cm, Undated; cuid1066 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Drinks/Beverages; Photographic Prints; Restaurants/bars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - A man standing in front of the Arc de Triomphe du Carrousel, Paris, France. 8.3 x 11.0 cm, Undated; cuid1067 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Photographic Prints; Animals; Individual Portraits; Statues/Sculptures; Gelatin Silver Prints; Monuments/Memorials; Horses; Men; Paris, France; Facial Hair; Hats; Streets/Roads
    - Mansour Beih series - the Palais du Trocadéro - Trocadero Palace (same handwriting as ref1081 and ref1082). 11.5 x 7.1 cm, Undated; cuid1068 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Bridges; Rivers; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Paris, France; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Palaces; Landscapes
  - Cologne Series, 1415
    - Cologne Series - The St. Aposteln Church, Neumarkt, Cologne, Germany. 7.3 x 10.1 cm, Undated; cuid1079 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Religious Sites; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Churches; Cologne, Germany; English Writing; Individual Portraits
    - Cologne Series - A man standing in front of a fountain in Neumarkt, Cologne. 7.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated; cuid1080 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Fountains; Shops; Men; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Children; Cologne, Germany
    - Cologne Series - A man standing on the Kaiser Wilhelm (Cologne) Ring in Cologne, Germany. 7.8 x 10.3 cm, Undated; cuid1081 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Cologne, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Buildings; Fountains; Men; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Cologne Series - A man standing on the Kaiser Wilhelm Ring in Cologne, Germany. 7.8 x 10.2 cm, Undated; cuid1082 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Men; Fountains; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cologne, Germany; English Writing; Individual Portraits; Shops
  - Heavy Machinery Series, 1416
    - Heavy Machinery Series - A man poking his head through the center of a tire. 4.6 x 4.7 cm, Undated; cuid1042 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Agriculture/Farms; Facial Hair
    - Heavy Machinery Series - A man sitting in the back of a trailer, with oil drums nearby. 4.7 x 4.7 cm, Undated; cuid1043 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Horses; Animals; Egypt; Agriculture/Farms; Facial Hair
    - Heavy Machinery Series - A man sitting on a tractor. 4.7 x 4.7 cm, Undated; cuid1044 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Photographic Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Agriculture/Farms; Facial Hair
    - Heavy Machinery Series - A man standing in front of a harvester. 4.5 x 4.5 cm, Undated; cuid1045 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Men; Photographic Prints; Construction; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Agriculture/Farms; Facial Hair
    - Heavy Machinery Series - Three men on a steamroller. 4.6 x 4.7 cm, Undated; cuid1046 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Egypt; Photographic Prints; Construction; Men; Countryside/Rural; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Agriculture/Farms
    - Heavy Machinery Series - A road-building scene, with a steam roller in the background. 6.3 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid1047 (Box 5, Folder 17)